<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<entity-engine-xml>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-999">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the match string is not found in the HTML content.
Check the HTML content by using the View Source command from a browser.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-998">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the server does not accept the connection.
Check that the server and server process are running.
Check the load on the server.
Check the load on the network.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-997">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when DNS cannot find an IP address for a name.
Check the network connection to the DNS server.
Check that the DNS server for that domain is running.
Check that DNS is properly configured on the SiteView machine.
Check that the name exists in the configuration for that domain.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-996">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when a connection is made but not completed.
Check the load on the network.
Check the load on the server.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-995">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the content of a URL changes.
Check the URL using a browser to view the new contents.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-994">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when a Windows library has an internal problem.
If this problem occurs repeatedly, please report it to support@dragonflow.com
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-993">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when there is not a network path that reaches the server.
Check the network connection to the server.
Check that firewalls and routers allow access to the server.
Check the load on the network.
Check that the server is running.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-991">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the server returns an incomplete response.
It may be caused by a busy server or network.
It may also be caused by a problem in a CGI script.
Check the URL using a browser for additional information.
Check the load on the network.
Check the load on the server.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-990">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when a link, form, or frame is not found in the HTML on a page.
Check the HTML content for that step by using the View Source command from a browser.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-989">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when an error string is found in the HTML content.
Check the HTML content by using the View Source command from a browser.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-988">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the value of an item in an XML document is incorrect
Check the XML content by using the View Source command from a browser.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-987">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when a syntax problem is found in the XML content.
Check the XML content by using the View Source command from a browser.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="-986">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when an item is not found in the XML content.
Check the XML content by using the View Source command from a browser.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="400">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned by CGI scripts or other programs that create web pages.
It may also be returned by a web server that is having problems.
Check that the correct parameters are being passed.
Check the URL using a browser for additional information.
Check the web server error log for additional information.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="401">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the web server requires authorization information.
Check that the correct username and password as being sent.
Check that your IP address is allowed access to the server.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="403">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned by the web server when access to this URL is not allowed.
Check the web server configuration.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="404">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned by the web server when it cannot find the URL requested.
Check that the URL name and spelling are correct.
Check that the file exists on the web server.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="407">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the proxy server requires authorization information.
Check that the correct proxy username and password as being sent.
Check that your IP address is allowed access to the proxy.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="500">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned by CGI scripts or other programs that create web pages.
It may also be returned by a web server that is having problems.
Check that the correct parameters are being passed.
Check the URL using a browser for additional information.
Check the web server error log for additional information.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
    <SvMonitorStatusHelp id="503">
        <message><![CDATA[This message is returned when the web server it to busy to handle your request.
Check the CPU usage on your server.
Check for other processes that using resources.
]]></message>
    </SvMonitorStatusHelp>
</entity-engine-xml>
